<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News on Open Source</title><link>https://sktelecom.github.io/en/blog/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on Open Source</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://sktelecom.github.io/en/blog/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SK Telecom is the first Telecommunications Operator to adopt OpenChain ISO 5230</title><link>https://sktelecom.github.io/en/blog/2021/09/09/sk-telecom-is-the-first-telecommunications-operator-to-adopt-openchain-iso-5230/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sktelecom.github.io/en/blog/2021/09/09/sk-telecom-is-the-first-telecommunications-operator-to-adopt-openchain-iso-5230/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;SK Telecom, South Korea’s largest wireless carrier, is the first telecommunications operator to adopt OpenChain ISO 5230. This leap forward in governance builds on their long-term mission to lead in technological capabilities in 5G, AI, big data analysis, IoT and quantum cryptography communications as a global ICT leader.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class="card rounded p-2 td-post-card mb-4 mt-4" style="max-width: 910px"&gt;
&lt;img class="card-img-top" src="https://sktelecom.github.io/en/blog/2021/09/09/sk-telecom-is-the-first-telecommunications-operator-to-adopt-openchain-iso-5230/featured_sktlogo_hu_5466fd5e1247ceab.png" width="900" height="355"&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="card-body px-0 pt-2 pb-0"&gt;
&lt;p class="card-text"&gt;


&lt;small class="text-body-secondary"&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SK telecom&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“SK Telecom is preparing for its transition to an AI company, and is strategically using open source to develop advanced technologies in AI, 5G, and cloud technology”, says Kim Yoon, CTO, SK Telecom. “Open source, essential for the early introduction of new technologies and rapid technological change, forms a key part of our strategy. We adopted OpenChain ISO 5230, the International Standard for open source compliance, to ensure effective process management in this space. We are also spreading our know-how around complying with open source international standards to SK affiliates and software supply chains to drive further expansion of open source ecosystems and to deliver even greater social value.”&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>SRT Alliance Welcomes SKT to the SRT Open Source Video Streaming Project</title><link>https://sktelecom.github.io/en/blog/2021/03/30/srt-alliance-welcomes-skt-to-the-srt-open-source-video-streaming-project/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sktelecom.github.io/en/blog/2021/03/30/srt-alliance-welcomes-skt-to-the-srt-open-source-video-streaming-project/</guid><description>&lt;figure class="card rounded p-2 td-post-card mb-4 mt-4" style="max-width: 610px"&gt;
&lt;img class="card-img-top" src="https://sktelecom.github.io/en/blog/2021/03/30/srt-alliance-welcomes-skt-to-the-srt-open-source-video-streaming-project/featured-srtalliance_hu_e368627ed20acc6f.jpg" width="600" height="300"&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="card-body px-0 pt-2 pb-0"&gt;
&lt;p class="card-text"&gt;


Image credit: SRT Alliance

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MONTREAL, CANADA – March 30, 2021&lt;/strong&gt; – The &lt;a href="https://www.srtalliance.org/"&gt;SRT Alliance&lt;/a&gt;, established by &lt;a href="http://www.haivision.com/"&gt;Haivision&lt;/a&gt; (TSX: HAI), a leading global provider of mission-critical, real-time video streaming and networking solutions, today announced that SK Telecom (hereinafter referred to as “SKT”), Korea’s largest wireless telecommunications operator, has joined the SRT Alliance to support and adopt the SRT open source protocol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SRT (Secure Reliable Transport) is a free open source video transport protocol and technology stack originally developed and pioneered by Haivision that enables the delivery of high-quality and secure, low latency video across the public internet. With over 450 members in the SRT Alliance and widespread industry adoption, SRT is the fastest growing open source streaming project.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>