<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SKT Open Source – About</title>
    <link>/guide/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on SKT Open Source</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	  <atom:link href="/guide/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide: Kubeflow</title>
      <link>/guide/about/kubeflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guide/about/kubeflow/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The Kubeflow project is dedicated to making deployments of machine learning (ML)
workflows on Kubernetes simple, portable and scalable. Our goal is not to
recreate other services, but to provide a straightforward way to deploy
best-of-breed open-source systems for ML to diverse infrastructures. Anywhere
you are running Kubernetes, you should be able to run Kubeflow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-started-with-kubeflow&#34;&gt;Getting started with Kubeflow&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/started/kubeflow-overview/&#34;&gt;Kubeflow overview&lt;/a&gt; for an
introduction to the Kubeflow architecture and to see how you can use Kubeflow
to manage your ML workflow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/started/getting-started/&#34;&gt;getting-started guide&lt;/a&gt; to set up
your environment and install Kubeflow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watch the following video which provides an introduction to Kubeflow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/cTZArDgbIWw&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-kubeflow&#34;&gt;What is Kubeflow?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kubeflow is &lt;em&gt;the machine learning toolkit for Kubernetes&lt;/em&gt;. Learn about &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/about/use-cases/&#34;&gt;Kubeflow use cases&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To use Kubeflow, the basic workflow is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download and run the Kubeflow deployment binary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customize the resulting configuration files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run the specified script to deploy your containers to your specific
environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can adapt the configuration to choose the platforms and services that you
want to use for each stage of the ML workflow: data preparation, model training,
prediction serving, and service management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can choose to deploy your Kubernetes workloads locally, on-premises, or to
a cloud environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/started/kubeflow-overview/&#34;&gt;Kubeflow overview&lt;/a&gt; for more details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-kubeflow-mission&#34;&gt;The Kubeflow mission&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our goal is to make scaling machine learning (ML) models and deploying them to
production as simple as possible, by letting Kubernetes do what it&amp;rsquo;s great at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easy, repeatable, portable deployments on a diverse infrastructure
(for example, experimenting on a laptop, then moving to an on-premises
cluster or to the cloud)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deploying and managing loosely-coupled microservices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scaling based on demand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because ML practitioners use a diverse set of tools, one of the key goals is to
customize the stack based on user requirements (within reason) and let the
system take care of the &amp;ldquo;boring stuff&amp;rdquo;. While we have started with a narrow set
of technologies, we are working with many different projects to include
additional tooling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, we want to have a set of simple manifests that give you an easy to
use ML stack &lt;em&gt;anywhere&lt;/em&gt; Kubernetes is already running, and that can self
configure based on the cluster it deploys into.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;history&#34;&gt;History&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kubeflow started as an open sourcing of the way Google ran &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tensorflow.org/&#34;&gt;TensorFlow&lt;/a&gt; internally, based on a pipeline called &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tensorflow.org/tfx/&#34;&gt;TensorFlow Extended&lt;/a&gt;. It began as just a simpler way to run TensorFlow jobs on Kubernetes, but has since expanded to be a multi-architecture, multi-cloud framework for running entire machine learning pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;roadmaps&#34;&gt;Roadmaps&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see what&amp;rsquo;s coming up in future versions of Kubeflow, refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/kubeflow/blob/master/ROADMAP.md&#34;&gt;Kubeflow roadmap&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following components also have roadmaps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/arena/blob/master/ROADMAP.md&#34;&gt;Arena&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/fairing/blob/master/roadmap.md&#34;&gt;Fairing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/pipelines/blob/master/ROADMAP.md&#34;&gt;Kubeflow Pipelines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/kfserving/blob/master/ROADMAP.md&#34;&gt;KF Serving&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/katib/blob/master/ROADMAP.md&#34;&gt;Katib&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/mpi-operator/blob/master/ROADMAP.md&#34;&gt;MPI Operator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-involved&#34;&gt;Getting involved&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are many ways to contribute to Kubeflow, and we welcome contributions!
Read the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/about/contributing&#34;&gt;contributor&amp;rsquo;s guide&lt;/a&gt; to get started on the
code, and get to know the community in the
&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/about/community&#34;&gt;community guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide: Use Cases</title>
      <link>/guide/about/use-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guide/about/use-cases/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The end goal of every organization that utilizes machine learning (ML) is to have
their ML models successfully run in production and generate value to the
business. But what does it take to reach that point?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before a model ends up in production, there are potentially many steps required
to build and deploy an ML model: data loading, verification, splitting,
processing, feature engineering, model training and verification, hyperparameter
tuning, and model serving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, ML models can require more observation than traditional
applications, because your data inputs can drift over time. Manually rebuilding
models and data sets is time consuming and error prone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To simplify these requirements and challenges, we created Kubeflow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;deploying-and-managing-a-complex-ml-system-at-scale&#34;&gt;Deploying and managing a complex ML system at scale&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kubeflow is a scalable, portable, distributed ML platform that runs on
Kubernetes. This means that all capabilities of Kubernetes are available to a
Kubeflow user. With Kubeflow, you can manage the entire AI organization at scale
and still be able to maintain the same quality of control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kubeflow and Kubernetes provide consistent and efficient operations and
optimized infrastructure. Your researchers can have more time to focus on the
valuable tasks of developing domain specific intellectual property rather than
debugging DevOps configuration issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kubeflow’s core and ecosystem critical user journeys (CUJs) provide software
solutions for end-to-end workflows: build, train and deploy and/or develop a
model and create, run and explore a pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;experimentation-with-training-an-ml-model&#34;&gt;Experimentation with training an ML model&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rapid experimentation is critical to building high quality machine learning
models quickly. Kubeflow offers a user-friendly interface (UI) that allows you
to track and compare experiments. You can decide later on which experiment was
the best and use it as a main source for your future steps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, Kubeflow 1.1 provides stable software sub-systems for model
training, such as Jupyter notebooks and popular ML training operators—
TensorFlow and PyTorch that run efficiently and securely in Kubernetes isolated
namespaces. The ML training operators simplify configuration and operations of
scaling ML training tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kubeflow has also delivered Critical User Journeys (CUJs), such as the build,
train and deploy, which provide end-to-end workflows that speed development.
You can read more about the CUJs in the Kubeflow roadmap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;end-to-end-hybrid-and-multi-cloud-ml-workloads&#34;&gt;End to end hybrid and multi-cloud ML workloads&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The development of ML models can require hybrid and multi-cloud portability and
secure sharing between teams, clusters and clouds. Kubeflow is supported
by all major cloud providers and available for on-premises installation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you need to develop on your laptop, train with GPU on your on-prem cluster
and serve in the cloud, Kubeflow provides the portability to support fast
experimentation, rapid training and robust deployment in the same or
different environments with minimal operational overhead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tuning-the-model-hyperparameters-during-training&#34;&gt;Tuning the model hyperparameters during training&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the model development part hyperparameters are often hard to tune.
Tuning hyperparameters is critical for model performance and accuracy.
Manually configuring hyperparameters is time consuming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kubeflow’s hyperparameter tuner (Katib) provides an automated way to match
your objectives. This automation can save days of model testing compute time
(freeing up valuable infrastructure), and speed the delivery of improved models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;continuous-integration-and-deployment-cicd-for-ml&#34;&gt;Continuous integration and deployment (CI/CD) for ML&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kubeflow currently doesn’t have a dedicated tool for this purpose. But our users
have been using the Pipelines component and it worked really well for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kubeflow Pipelines can be used to create reproducible workflows.
These workflows automate the steps needed to build a ML workflow,
which delivers consistency, saves iteration time, and helps in debugging,
auditability and compliance requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;next-steps&#34;&gt;Next steps&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See these docs for more information on the topics covered above:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/components/katib/&#34;&gt;Hyperparameter tuning with Katib&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/components/training/&#34;&gt;Training models with operators&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kubeflow.org/docs/pipelines/&#34;&gt;Get started with Pipelines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/notebooks/&#34;&gt;Jupyter notebooks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bit.ly/kf_roadmap&#34;&gt;Kubeflow roadmap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide: Contributing to Kubeflow</title>
      <link>/guide/about/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guide/about/contributing/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Kubeflow project!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-started-as-a-kubeflow-contributor&#34;&gt;Getting started as a Kubeflow contributor&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This document is the single source of truth for how to contribute to the code base.
We&amp;rsquo;d love to accept your patches and contributions to this project. There are
just a few small guidelines you need to follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sign-the-cla&#34;&gt;Sign the CLA&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contributions to this project must be accompanied by a Contributor License Agreement (CLA).
You (or your employer) retain the copyright to your contribution.
This gives us permission to use and redistribute your contributions as
part of the project. Head over to &lt;a href=&#34;https://cla.developers.google.com/&#34;&gt;https://cla.developers.google.com/&lt;/a&gt; to see
your current agreements on file or to sign a new one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You generally only need to submit a CLA once, so if you&amp;rsquo;ve already submitted one
(even if it was for a different project), you probably don&amp;rsquo;t need to do it
again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;follow-the-code-of-conduct&#34;&gt;Follow the code of conduct&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please make sure to read and observe our &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/community/blob/master/CODE_OF_CONDUCT.md&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/community/blob/master/INCLUSIVITY.md&#34;&gt;inclusivity document&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;consider-participating-in-kubeflow-user-research&#34;&gt;Consider participating in Kubeflow user research&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maggie Lynn, a user experience researcher, is conducting user studies to
inform future developments for Kubeflow. These typically involve a one hour
study session conducted online with a thank you gift for providing your feedback.
As a member of the Kubeflow community, your feedback and expertise are
extremely valuable to us, so if you have time in the next month, please consider
participating. To gather your interest, availability, and some basic information
about you, please fill out this form where you’ll find out more details about
this research opportunity: &lt;a href=&#34;https://goo.gl/forms/sv5sRo3UfsgeUEjK2&#34;&gt;https://goo.gl/forms/sv5sRo3UfsgeUEjK2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;joining-the-community&#34;&gt;Joining the community&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow these instructions if you want to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become a member of the Kubeflow GitHub org (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become part of the Kubeflow build cop or release teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be recognized as an individual or organization contributing to Kubeflow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;joining-the-kubeflow-github-org&#34;&gt;Joining the Kubeflow GitHub Org&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: Anyone can contribute to Kubeflow, adding yourself as a member in &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/internal-acls/blob/master/github-orgs/kubeflow/org.yaml&#34;&gt;org.yaml&lt;/a&gt; is not a mandatory step.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before asking to join the community, we ask that you first make a small number of contributions
to demonstrate your intent to continue contributing to Kubeflow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are are a number of ways to contribute to Kubeflow&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submit PRs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;File issues reporting bugs or providing feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer questions on Slack or GitHub issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use this &lt;a href=&#34;http://devstats.kubeflow.org/d/9/developers-summary&#34;&gt;table&lt;/a&gt; to see how many contributions
you&amp;rsquo;ve made&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: This only counts GitHub related ways of contributing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you are ready to join&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send a PR adding yourself as a member in &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/internal-acls/blob/master/github-orgs/kubeflow/org.yaml#L19&#34;&gt;org.yaml&lt;/a&gt;. Follow the instructions in &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/internal-acls#joining-kubeflow-github-organization&#34;&gt;Joining the Kubeflow GitHub organization&lt;/a&gt; for more information about artifacts to include with your PR and how to test your PR.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After the PR is merged an admin will send you an invitation
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a manual process that&amp;rsquo;s generally run a couple times a week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If a week passes without receiving an invitation reach out on &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/C8Q0QJYNB/convo/CABQ2BWHW-1544147308.002500/&#34;&gt;kubeflow#community&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;companiesorganizations&#34;&gt;Companies/organizations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like your company or organization to be acknowledged for contributing to
Kubeflow or participating in the community (being a user counts) please send a PR
adding the relevant info to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/community/blob/master/member_organizations.yaml&#34;&gt;member_organizations.yaml&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want your employee&amp;rsquo;s GitHub contributions to be attributed to your company please ask them to set
the company field in their GitHub profile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;community-discussions&#34;&gt;Community discussions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are many ways to contribute! Join one of our communication channels,
attend a community meeting, get to know the community. Read the details in
our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/about/community&#34;&gt;community guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;your-first-contribution&#34;&gt;Your first contribution&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;find-something-to-work-on&#34;&gt;Find something to work on&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Help is always welcome! For example, documentation (like the text you are reading
now) can always use improvement. There&amp;rsquo;s always code that can be clarified and
variables or functions that can be renamed or commented. There&amp;rsquo;s always a need
for more test coverage. You get the idea - if you ever see something you think
should be fixed, you should own it. Here is how you get started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;starter-issues&#34;&gt;Starter issues&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find Kubeflow issues that make good entry points:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start with issues labeled &lt;strong&gt;good first issue&lt;/strong&gt;. For example, see the good
first issues in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/website/issues?utf8=%E2%9C%93&amp;amp;q=is%3Aissue+is%3Aopen+label%3A%22good+first+issue%22&#34;&gt;kubeflow/website
repository&lt;/a&gt;
for doc updates, and in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/kubeflow/issues?utf8=%E2%9C%93&amp;amp;q=is%3Aissue+is%3Aopen+label%3A%22good+first+issue%22&#34;&gt;kubeflow/kubeflow
repository&lt;/a&gt;
for updates to the core Kubeflow code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For issues that require deeper knowledge of one or more technical aspects,
look at issues labeled &lt;strong&gt;help wanted&lt;/strong&gt;. For example, see these issues in the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/kubeflow/issues?utf8=%E2%9C%93&amp;amp;q=is%3Aissue+is%3Aopen+label%3A%22help+wanted%22&#34;&gt;kubeflow/kubeflow
repository&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examine the issues in any of the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow&#34;&gt;Kubeflow repositories&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;owners-files-and-pr-workflow&#34;&gt;Owners files and PR workflow&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our PR workflow is nearly identical to Kubernetes&amp;rsquo;. Most of these instructions are a
modified version of Kubernetes&amp;rsquo; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/blob/master/contributors/guide/README.md&#34;&gt;contributors&lt;/a&gt;
and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/blob/master/contributors/guide/owners.md#code-review-using-owners-files&#34;&gt;owners&lt;/a&gt;
guides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;overview-of-owners-files&#34;&gt;Overview of OWNERS files&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OWNERS files are used to designate responsibility over different parts of the Kubeflow codebase.
Today, we use them to assign the &lt;strong&gt;reviewer&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;approver&lt;/strong&gt; roles used in our two-phase code
review process. Our OWNERS files were inspired by &lt;a href=&#34;https://chromium.googlesource.com/chromium/src/+/master/docs/code_reviews.md&#34;&gt;Chromium OWNERS
files&lt;/a&gt;, which in turn
inspired &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.github.com/articles/about-codeowners/&#34;&gt;GitHub&amp;rsquo;s CODEOWNERS files&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The velocity of a project that uses code review is limited by the number of people capable of
reviewing code. The quality of a person&amp;rsquo;s code review is limited by their familiarity with the code
under review. Our goal is to address both of these concerns through the prudent use and maintenance
of OWNERS files&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;owners-a-nameowners-1a&#34;&gt;OWNERS &lt;a name=&#34;owners-1&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each directory that contains a unit of independent code or content may also contain an OWNERS file.
This file applies to everything within the directory, including the OWNERS file itself, sibling
files, and child directories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OWNERS files are in YAML format and support the following keys:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;approvers&lt;/code&gt;: a list of GitHub usernames or aliases that can &lt;code&gt;/approve&lt;/code&gt; a PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;labels&lt;/code&gt;: a list of GitHub labels to automatically apply to a PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;options&lt;/code&gt;: a map of options for how to interpret this OWNERS file, currently only one:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;no_parent_owners&lt;/code&gt;: defaults to &lt;code&gt;false&lt;/code&gt; if not present; if &lt;code&gt;true&lt;/code&gt;, exclude parent OWNERS files.
Allows the use case where &lt;code&gt;a/deep/nested/OWNERS&lt;/code&gt; file prevents &lt;code&gt;a/OWNERS&lt;/code&gt; file from having any
effect on &lt;code&gt;a/deep/nested/bit/of/code&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;reviewers&lt;/code&gt;: a list of GitHub usernames or aliases that are good candidates to &lt;code&gt;/lgtm&lt;/code&gt; a PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All users are expected to be assignable. In GitHub terms, this means they are either collaborators
of the repo, or members of the organization to which the repo belongs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A typical OWNERS file looks like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;approvers:
  - alice
  - bob     # this is a comment
reviewers:
  - alice
  - carol   # this is another comment
  - sig-foo # this is an alias
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;h4 id=&#34;owners_aliases&#34;&gt;OWNERS_ALIASES&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each repo may contain at its root an OWNERS_ALIAS file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OWNERS_ALIAS files are in YAML format and support the following keys:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;aliases&lt;/code&gt;: a mapping of alias name to a list of GitHub usernames&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We use aliases for groups instead of GitHub Teams, because changes to GitHub Teams are not
publicly auditable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A sample OWNERS_ALIASES file looks like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;aliases:
  sig-foo:
    - david
    - erin
  sig-bar:
    - bob
    - frank
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;GitHub usernames and aliases listed in OWNERS files are case-insensitive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-code-review-process&#34;&gt;The code review process&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;author&lt;/strong&gt; submits a PR&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phase 0: Automation suggests &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;approvers&lt;/strong&gt; for the PR&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determine the set of OWNERS files nearest to the code being changed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose at least two suggested &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt;, trying to find a unique reviewer for every leaf
OWNERS file, and request their reviews on the PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose suggested &lt;strong&gt;approvers&lt;/strong&gt;, one from each OWNERS file, and list them in a comment on the PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phase 1: Humans review the PR&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; look for general code quality, correctness, sane software engineering, style, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anyone in the organization can act as a &lt;strong&gt;reviewer&lt;/strong&gt; with the exception of the individual who
opened the PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the code changes look good to them, a &lt;strong&gt;reviewer&lt;/strong&gt; types &lt;code&gt;/lgtm&lt;/code&gt; in a PR comment or review;
if they change their mind, they &lt;code&gt;/lgtm cancel&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once a &lt;strong&gt;reviewer&lt;/strong&gt; has &lt;code&gt;/lgtm&lt;/code&gt;&#39;ed, &lt;a href=&#34;https://prow.k8s.io&#34;&gt;prow&lt;/a&gt;
(&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k8s-ci-robot/&#34;&gt;@k8s-ci-robot&lt;/a&gt;) applies an &lt;code&gt;lgtm&lt;/code&gt; label to the PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phase 2: Humans approve the PR&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The PR &lt;strong&gt;author&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;code&gt;/assign&lt;/code&gt;&#39;s all suggested &lt;strong&gt;approvers&lt;/strong&gt; to the PR, and optionally notifies
them (eg: &amp;ldquo;pinging @foo for approval&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only people listed in the relevant OWNERS files, either directly or through an alias, can act
as &lt;strong&gt;approvers&lt;/strong&gt;, including the individual who opened the PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approvers&lt;/strong&gt; look for holistic acceptance criteria, including dependencies with other features,
forwards/backwards compatibility, API and flag definitions, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the code changes look good to them, an &lt;strong&gt;approver&lt;/strong&gt; types &lt;code&gt;/approve&lt;/code&gt; in a PR comment or
review; if they change their mind, they &lt;code&gt;/approve cancel&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://prow.k8s.io&#34;&gt;prow&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k8s-ci-robot/&#34;&gt;@k8s-ci-robot&lt;/a&gt;) updates its
comment in the PR to indicate which &lt;strong&gt;approvers&lt;/strong&gt; still need to approve&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once all &lt;strong&gt;approvers&lt;/strong&gt; (one from each of the previously identified OWNERS files) have approved,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://prow.k8s.io&#34;&gt;prow&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k8s-ci-robot/&#34;&gt;@k8s-ci-robot&lt;/a&gt;) applies an
&lt;code&gt;approved&lt;/code&gt; label&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phase 3: Automation merges the PR:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If all of the following are true:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All required labels are present (eg: &lt;code&gt;lgtm&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;approved&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any blocking labels are missing (eg: there is no &lt;code&gt;do-not-merge/hold&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;needs-rebase&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if any of the following are true:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;there are no presubmit prow jobs configured for this repo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;there are presubmit prow jobs configured for this repo, and they all pass after automatically
being re-run one last time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then the PR will automatically be merged&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;quirks-of-the-process&#34;&gt;Quirks of the process&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a number of behaviors we&amp;rsquo;ve observed that while &lt;em&gt;possible&lt;/em&gt; are discouraged, as they go
against the intent of this review process. Some of these could be prevented in the future, but this
is the state of today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An &lt;strong&gt;approver&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;rsquo;s &lt;code&gt;/lgtm&lt;/code&gt; is simultaneously interpreted as an &lt;code&gt;/approve&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While a convenient shortcut for some, it can be surprising that the same command is interpreted
in one of two ways depending on who the commenter is&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Instead, explicitly write out &lt;code&gt;/lgtm&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;/approve&lt;/code&gt; to help observers, or save the &lt;code&gt;/lgtm&lt;/code&gt; for
a &lt;strong&gt;reviewer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This goes against the idea of having at least two sets of eyes on a PR, and may be a sign that
there are too few &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; (who aren&amp;rsquo;t also &lt;strong&gt;approver&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technically, anyone who is a member of the Kubeflow GitHub organization can drive-by &lt;code&gt;/lgtm&lt;/code&gt; a
PR
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive-by reviews from non-members are encouraged as a way of demonstrating experience and
intent to become a collaborator or reviewer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive-by &lt;code&gt;/lgtm&lt;/code&gt;&#39;s from members may be a sign that our OWNERS files are too small, or that the
existing &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; are too unresponsive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This goes against the idea of specifying &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; in the first place, to ensure that
&lt;strong&gt;author&lt;/strong&gt; is getting actionable feedback from people knowledgeable with the code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reviewers&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;approvers&lt;/strong&gt; are unresponsive
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This causes a lot of frustration for &lt;strong&gt;authors&lt;/strong&gt; who often have little visibility into why their
PR is being ignored&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;approvers&lt;/strong&gt; are so overloaded by GitHub notifications that @mention&amp;rsquo;ing
is unlikely to get a quick response&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If an &lt;strong&gt;author&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;code&gt;/assign&lt;/code&gt;&#39;s a PR, &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;approvers&lt;/strong&gt; will be made aware of it on
their &lt;a href=&#34;https://k8s-gubernator.appspot.com/pr&#34;&gt;PR dashboard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An &lt;strong&gt;author&lt;/strong&gt; can work around this by manually reading the relevant OWNERS files,
&lt;code&gt;/unassign&lt;/code&gt;&#39;ing unresponsive individuals, and &lt;code&gt;/assign&lt;/code&gt;&#39;ing others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a sign that our OWNERS files are stale; pruning the &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;approvers&lt;/strong&gt; lists
would help with this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is the PR &lt;strong&gt;authors&lt;/strong&gt; responsibility to drive a PR to resolution. This means if the PR &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; are unresponsive they should escalate as noted below
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;e.g ping &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; in a timely manner to get it reviewed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; don&amp;rsquo;t respond look at the OWNERs file in root and ping &lt;strong&gt;approvers&lt;/strong&gt; listed there&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Authors&lt;/strong&gt; are unresponsive
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This costs a tremendous amount of attention as context for an individual PR is lost over time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This hurts the project in general as its general noise level increases over time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Instead, close PR&amp;rsquo;s that are untouched after too long (we currently have a bot do this after 90
days)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;automation-using-owners-files&#34;&gt;Automation using OWNERS files&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;prowhttpsgitk8siotest-infraprow&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git.k8s.io/test-infra/prow&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;prow&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prow receives events from GitHub, and reacts to them. It is effectively stateless. The following
pieces of prow are used to implement the code review process above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git.k8s.io/test-infra/prow/cmd/tide&#34;&gt;cmd: tide&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;per-repo configuration:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;labels&lt;/code&gt;: list of labels required to be present for merge (eg: &lt;code&gt;lgtm&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;missingLabels&lt;/code&gt;: list of labels required to be missing for merge (eg: &lt;code&gt;do-not-merge/hold&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;reviewApprovedRequired&lt;/code&gt;: defaults to &lt;code&gt;false&lt;/code&gt;; when true, require that there must be at least
one &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.github.com/articles/about-pull-request-reviews/&#34;&gt;approved pull request review&lt;/a&gt;
present for merge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;merge_method&lt;/code&gt;: defaults to &lt;code&gt;merge&lt;/code&gt;; when &lt;code&gt;squash&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;rebase&lt;/code&gt;, use that merge method instead
when clicking a PR&amp;rsquo;s merge button&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;merges PR&amp;rsquo;s once they meet the appropriate criteria as configured above&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;if there are any presubmit prow jobs for the repo the PR is against, they will be re-run one
final time just prior to merge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git.k8s.io/test-infra/prow/plugins/assign&#34;&gt;plugin: assign&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;assigns GitHub users in response to &lt;code&gt;/assign&lt;/code&gt; comments on a PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;unassigns GitHub users in response to &lt;code&gt;/unassign&lt;/code&gt; comments on a PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git.k8s.io/test-infra/prow/plugins/approve&#34;&gt;plugin: approve&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;per-repo configuration:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;issue_required&lt;/code&gt;: defaults to &lt;code&gt;false&lt;/code&gt;; when &lt;code&gt;true&lt;/code&gt;, require that the PR description link to
an issue, or that at least one &lt;strong&gt;approver&lt;/strong&gt; issues a &lt;code&gt;/approve no-issue&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;implicit_self_approve&lt;/code&gt;: defaults to &lt;code&gt;false&lt;/code&gt;; when &lt;code&gt;true&lt;/code&gt;, if the PR author is in relevant
OWNERS files, act as if they have implicitly &lt;code&gt;/approve&lt;/code&gt;&#39;d&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;adds the &lt;code&gt;approved&lt;/code&gt; label once an &lt;strong&gt;approver&lt;/strong&gt; for each of the required
OWNERS files has &lt;code&gt;/approve&lt;/code&gt;&#39;d&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;comments as required OWNERS files are satisfied&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;removes outdated approval status comments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git.k8s.io/test-infra/prow/plugins/blunderbuss&#34;&gt;plugin: blunderbuss&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;determines &lt;strong&gt;reviewers&lt;/strong&gt; and requests their reviews on PR&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git.k8s.io/test-infra/prow/plugins/lgtm&#34;&gt;plugin: lgtm&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;adds the &lt;code&gt;lgtm&lt;/code&gt; label when a &lt;strong&gt;reviewer&lt;/strong&gt; comments &lt;code&gt;/lgtm&lt;/code&gt; on a PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the &lt;strong&gt;PR author&lt;/strong&gt; may not &lt;code&gt;/lgtm&lt;/code&gt; their own PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git.k8s.io/test-infra/prow/repoowners/repoowners.go&#34;&gt;pkg: k8s.io/test-infra/prow/repoowners&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;parses OWNERS and OWNERS_ALIAS files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;if the &lt;code&gt;no_parent_owners&lt;/code&gt; option is encountered, parent owners are excluded from having
any influence over files adjacent to or underneath of the current OWNERS file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;maintaining-owners-files&#34;&gt;Maintaining OWNERS files&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OWNERS files should be regularly maintained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We encourage people to self-nominate or self-remove from OWNERS files via PR&amp;rsquo;s. Ideally in the future
we could use metrics-driven automation to assist in this process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We should strive to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;grow the number of OWNERS files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;add new people to OWNERS files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ensure OWNERS files only contain org members and repo collaborators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ensure OWNERS files only contain people are actively contributing to or reviewing the code they own&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;remove inactive people from OWNERS files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bad examples of OWNERS usage:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;directories that lack OWNERS files, resulting in too many hitting root OWNERS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OWNERS files that have a single person as both approver and reviewer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OWNERS files that haven&amp;rsquo;t been touched in over 6 months&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OWNERS files that have non-collaborators present&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good examples of OWNERS usage:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;there are more &lt;code&gt;reviewers&lt;/code&gt; than &lt;code&gt;approvers&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the &lt;code&gt;approvers&lt;/code&gt; are not in the &lt;code&gt;reviewers&lt;/code&gt; section&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OWNERS files that are regularly updated (at least once per release)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide: Community</title>
      <link>/guide/about/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guide/about/community/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;In the interest of fostering an open and welcoming environment, we as
contributors and maintainers pledge to make participation in our project and
our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body
size, disability, ethnicity, gender identity and expression, level of
experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance,
race, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kubeflow community is guided by our &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/community/blob/master/CODE_OF_CONDUCT.md&#34;&gt;Code of
Conduct&lt;/a&gt;,
which we encourage everybody to read before participating. We hold our leaders
accountable for the guidelines in
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/community/blob/master/INCLUSIVITY.md&#34;&gt;this document&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome-to-all-google-summer-of-code-gsoc-participants&#34;&gt;Welcome to all Google Summer of Code (GSoC) participants&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kubeflow community is delighted to be part of
&lt;strong&gt;Google Summer of Code 2020&lt;/strong&gt;. Community
mentors look forward to working with students on their GSoC projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/about/gsoc/&#34;&gt;Visit the Kubeflow GSoC page&lt;/a&gt; to find handy information and
links for GSoC students and mentors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;community-discussions&#34;&gt;Community discussions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are many ways to contribute! Join one of our communication channels,
attend a community meeting, get to know the community, discuss updates, suggest
exciting new integrations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;community-meetings&#34;&gt;Community meetings&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://calendar.google.com/calendar/embed?src=kubeflow.org_7l5vnbn8suj2se10sen81d9428%40group.calendar.google.com&amp;amp;ctz=America%2FLos_Angeles&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting calendar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;https://calendar.google.com/calendar/ical/kubeflow.org_7l5vnbn8suj2se10sen81d9428%40group.calendar.google.com/public/basic.ics&#34;&gt;iCal version&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bit.ly/kf-meeting-notes&#34;&gt;Meeting notes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your group has a regular meeting, talk to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ewilderj&#34;&gt;@ewilderj&lt;/a&gt; about getting it added to the calendar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;kubeflow-community-call&#34;&gt;Kubeflow community call&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project team holds a weekly community call on Tuesdays. This call alternates
weekly between US East/EMEA and US West/APAC friendly times. Joining the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/kubeflow-discuss&#34;&gt;kubeflow-discuss&lt;/a&gt;
mailing list will automatically send you calendar invitations for the meetings,
or you can subscribe to the community meeting calendar above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Agenda, notes, and a reminder of the next call are sent to the kubeflow-discuss
mailing list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id=&#34;slack&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;slack-community-and-channels&#34;&gt;Slack community and channels&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kubeflow Slack workspace is
&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/&#34;&gt;kubeflow.slack.com&lt;/a&gt;. To join, click this
&lt;a href=&#34;https://join.slack.com/t/kubeflow/shared_invite/zt-cpr020z4-PfcAue_2nw67~iIDy7maAQ&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;invitation to our Slack
workspace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kubeflow Slack workspace offers several channels. Here are a few examples:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Topic&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Slack channel&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;General discussion&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/C7REE0EHK&#34;&gt;#general&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Community meeting chat&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/C8Q0QJYNB&#34;&gt;#community&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;WG AutoML (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/community/tree/master/wg-automl&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/C018PMV53NW&#34;&gt;#wg-automl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;WG Training (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/community/tree/master/wg-training&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/C018N3M6QKB&#34;&gt;#wg-training&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;KFServing (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/kfserving&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/CH6E58LNP&#34;&gt;#kfserving&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Pipelines (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/pipelines&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/CE10KS9M4&#34;&gt;#kubeflow-pipelines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Examples (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/examples&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/CA30Q9A4U&#34;&gt;#kubeflow-examples&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Documentation (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/website&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/CA4M298LD&#34;&gt;#website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Product management&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/CGP3DKT5E&#34;&gt;#product-management&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Google Summer of Code (GSoC)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/CUF1GCJ4Q&#34;&gt;#gsoc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;mailing-lists&#34;&gt;Mailing lists&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The primary mailing list (email group) is
&lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/kubeflow-discuss&#34;&gt;kubeflow-discuss&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More detail about the Kubeflow mailing lists:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Topic&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Mailing list&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;General discussion&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/kubeflow-discuss&#34;&gt;kubeflow-discuss&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-should-consider-contributing-to-kubeflow&#34;&gt;Who should consider contributing to Kubeflow?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folks who want to add support for other ML frameworks (e.g. PyTorch, XGBoost, scikit-learn)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folks who want to bring more Kubernetes magic to ML (e.g. ISTIO integration for prediction)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folks who want to make Kubeflow a richer ML platform (e.g. support for ML pipelines, hyperparameter tuning, neural architecture search)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folks who want to tune Kubeflow for their particular Kubernetes distribution or Cloud&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folks who want to write tutorials or blog posts showing how to use Kubeflow to solve ML problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For details on contributing please look at &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/about/contributing/&#34;&gt;the contributor&amp;rsquo;s guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide: Google Summer of Code</title>
      <link>/guide/about/gsoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guide/about/gsoc/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;/docs/images/gsoc-icon-192.png&#34; 
    alt=&#34;The Google Summer of Code icon&#34;
    class=&#34;mt-1 mb-3 float-right img-fluid&#34;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kubeflow community is delighted to be part of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://summerofcode.withgoogle.com/&#34;&gt;Google Summer of Code (GSoC) 2020&lt;/a&gt;. Community
mentors look forward to working with students on their GSoC projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Top links:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://summerofcode.withgoogle.com/how-it-works/#timeline&#34;&gt;GSoC timeline&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1AQDD9s8VpCf3y8OLKTBSMgDzHSjdsV_DOyL5dc-XCOQ/&#34;&gt;Kubeflow GSoC project
ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1dnhvxFLV1odqpqdWdujUNNUhVPSykflLy2nLJCz-Yws/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Kubeflow template for project
proposals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;information-for-students&#34;&gt;Information for students&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The GSoC student application phase is now closed and student selection is in
progress. See the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://summerofcode.withgoogle.com/how-it-works/#timeline&#34;&gt;GSoC timeline&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re still welcome to explore Kubeflow. Kubeflow welcomes contributions
at any time, whether within or outside the framework of GSoC. See the
&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/about/community/&#34;&gt;community page&lt;/a&gt; for Slack channels, mailing lists,
meetings, and other ways to connect with the Kubeflow community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information about GSoC, see the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.google.com/open-source/gsoc/faq&#34;&gt;GSoC docs&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.google.com/open-source/gsoc/resources/guide&#34;&gt;guides&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;information-for-mentors&#34;&gt;Information for mentors&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to all mentors who&amp;rsquo;re interested in helping a GSoC student with their
Kubeflow project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get started:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read the &lt;a href=&#34;https://google.github.io/gsocguides/mentor/&#34;&gt;Google Summer of Code mentor
guide&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.google.com/open-source/gsoc/help/responsibilities&#34;&gt;roles and
responsibilities&lt;/a&gt;
to understand what is expected of you over the next 6 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bookmark the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://summerofcode.withgoogle.com/how-it-works/#timeline&#34;&gt;GSoC timeline&lt;/a&gt;
and be prepared to take action in time for the milestones shown on the
timeline, and to help your students meet the deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch the 5 minute YouTube video: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3J_eBuYxcyg&#34;&gt;Being a Great GSoC
Mentor&lt;/a&gt;. The video was shot with
GSoC veteran org admins and mentors. It contains helpful information about the
program and how to participate successfully at each step in GSoC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re not registered as a mentor, email
&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:kubeflow-gsoc-admin@kubeflow.org&#34;&gt;kubeflow-gsoc-admin@kubeflow.org&lt;/a&gt;
to indicate your interest in mentoring a student during GSoC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you receive an invitation, follow the link in the email to register on the
GSoC program site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examine the student proposals. Click &lt;strong&gt;want to mentor&lt;/strong&gt; on the proposals
that you&amp;rsquo;d like to mentor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start chatting to students:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubeflow.slack.com/messages/CUF1GCJ4Q&#34;&gt;#gsoc&lt;/a&gt; channel on Kubeflow
Slack and answer students&amp;rsquo; questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respond to students&amp;rsquo; questions on the Kubeflow mentors mailing list
(&lt;code&gt;kubeflow-gsoc-mentors@kubeflow.org&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information about GSoC, see the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.google.com/open-source/gsoc/faq&#34;&gt;GSoC docs&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.google.com/open-source/gsoc/resources/guide&#34;&gt;guides&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;mailing-lists&#34;&gt;Mailing lists&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are the Kubeflow mailing lists related to GSoC:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:kubeflow-gsoc-mentors@kubeflow.org&#34;&gt;kubeflow-gsoc-mentors@kubeflow.org&lt;/a&gt;:
The mentor mailing list for Kubeflow GSoC projects.
Students can email this group to receive feedback on project proposals.
Mentors and org administrators can use this group to discuss Kubeflow GSoC
matters. Group members are Kubeflow GSoC mentors and org administrators.
Messages are visible to sender, CCs, and group members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:kubeflow-gsoc-admin@kubeflow.org&#34;&gt;kubeflow-gsoc-admin@kubeflow.org&lt;/a&gt;:
The organization administrator mailing list for Kubeflow&amp;rsquo;s participation in
GSoC.
Students and mentors can email this group to raise Kubeflow GSoC matters with
the administrators. Group members are Kubeflow GSoC org administrators only.
Messages are visible to sender, CCs, and group members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/kubeflow-discuss&#34;&gt;kubeflow-discuss&lt;/a&gt;:
Kubeflow&amp;rsquo;s primarily mailing list and discussion group. See the
&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/about/community/&#34;&gt;community page&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide: Docs</title>
      <link>/guide/about/docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guide/about/docs/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Kubeflow documentation!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kubeflow docs are published at
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kubeflow.org/&#34;&gt;www.kubeflow.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The source for the docs is in the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/website/&#34;&gt;kubeflow/website repo&lt;/a&gt; on GitHub.
We use &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; to format and generate our website, and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.netlify.com/&#34;&gt;Netlify&lt;/a&gt; to manage the deployment of the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;versioning&#34;&gt;Versioning&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kubeflow.org&#34;&gt;www.kubeflow.org&lt;/a&gt; points to the &lt;strong&gt;master&lt;/strong&gt; branch of the docs. You can access
other versions by clicking the version dropdown at top right of the website
menu bar:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/docs/images/version-dropdown.png&#34; 
alt=&#34;Version dropdown&#34;
style=&#34;width:30%;&#34;
class=&#34;mt-3 mb-3 border border-info rounded&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We create a new branch of the docs for each stable release of Kubeflow.
For example, the docs for the v0.2 stable release are on published on the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://v0-2.kubeflow.org/docs/about/kubeflow/&#34;&gt;v0.2 website&lt;/a&gt;, which
corresponds to the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/website/tree/v0.2-branch&#34;&gt;v0.2-branch&lt;/a&gt; on
GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;contributing-to-the-docs&#34;&gt;Contributing to the docs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We welcome updates to the docs! Please help us make them better. Small fixes,
typos, bug fixes, plugging gaps—all are useful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For help with getting started, take a look at the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/website/blob/master/README.md&#34;&gt;README&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For guidance on writing effective documentation, see the
&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/about/style-guide/&#34;&gt;style guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide: Style Guide for the Kubeflow Docs</title>
      <link>/guide/about/style-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guide/about/style-guide/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This style guide is for the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kubeflow.org/docs/&#34;&gt;Kubeflow documentation&lt;/a&gt;.
The style guide helps contributors to write documentation that
readers can understand quickly and correctly. The Kubeflow docs aim for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consistency in style and terminology, so that readers can expect certain
structures and conventions. Readers don&amp;rsquo;t have to keep re-learning how to use
the documentation or questioning whether they&amp;rsquo;ve understood something
correctly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clear, concise writing so that readers can quickly find and understand the
information they need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-standard-american-spelling&#34;&gt;Use standard American spelling&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use American spelling rather than Commonwealth or British spelling.
Refer to &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.merriam-webster.com/&#34;&gt;Merriam-Webster&amp;rsquo;s Collegiate Dictionary, Eleventh
Edition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-capital-letters-sparingly&#34;&gt;Use capital letters sparingly&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some hints:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capitalize only the first letter of each heading within the page. (That is,
use sentence case.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capitalize (almost) every word in page titles. (That is, use title case.) The
little words like &amp;ldquo;and&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;in&amp;rdquo;, etc, don&amp;rsquo;t get a capital letter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In page content, use capitals only for brand names, like Kubeflow, Kubernetes,
and so on. See more about brand names &lt;a href=&#34;#brand-names&#34;&gt;below&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t use capital letters to emphasize words.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;spell-out-abbreviations-and-acronyms-on-first-use&#34;&gt;Spell out abbreviations and acronyms on first use&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Always spell out the full term for every abbreviation or acronym the first time
you use it on the page. Don&amp;rsquo;t assume people know what an abbreviation or acronym
means, even if it seems like common knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example: &amp;ldquo;To run Kubernetes locally in a virtual machine (VM)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-contractions-if-you-want-to&#34;&gt;Use contractions if you want to&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, it&amp;rsquo;s fine to write &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; instead of &amp;ldquo;it is&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id=&#34;brand-names&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-full-correct-brand-names&#34;&gt;Use full, correct brand names&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When referring to a product or brand, use the full name. Capitalize the
name as the product owners do in the product documentation. Do
not use abbreviations even if they&amp;rsquo;re in common use, unless the product owner
has sanctioned the abbreviation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&#34;table table-bordered&#34;&gt;
    &lt;thead class=&#34;thead-light&#34;&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Use this&lt;/th&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Instead of this&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/thead&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;Kubeflow&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;kubeflow&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;k8s&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;ksonnet&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;Ksonnet&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;be-consistent-with-punctuation&#34;&gt;Be consistent with punctuation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use punctuation consistently within a page. For example, if you use a period
(full stop) after every item in list, then use a period on all other lists on
the page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check the other pages if you&amp;rsquo;re unsure about a particular convention.
Examples:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Most pages in the Kubeflow docs use a period at the end of every list item.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is no period at the end of the page subtitle and the subtitle need not
be a full sentence. (The subtitle comes from the &lt;code&gt;description&lt;/code&gt; in the front
matter of each page.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-active-voice-rather-than-passive-voice&#34;&gt;Use active voice rather than passive voice&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Passive voice is often confusing, as it&amp;rsquo;s not clear who should perform the
action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&#34;table table-bordered&#34;&gt;
    &lt;thead class=&#34;thead-light&#34;&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Use active voice&lt;/th&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Instead of passive voice&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/thead&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;You can configure Kubeflow to&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;Kubeflow can be configured to&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;Add the directory to your path&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;The directory should be added to your path&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-simple-present-tense&#34;&gt;Use simple present tense&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Avoid future tense (&amp;ldquo;will&amp;rdquo;) and complex syntax such as conjunctive mood
(&amp;ldquo;would&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;should&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&#34;table table-bordered&#34;&gt;
    &lt;thead class=&#34;thead-light&#34;&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Use simple present tense&lt;/th&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Instead of future tense or complex syntax&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/thead&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;The following command provisions a virtual machine&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;The following command will provision a virtual machine&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;If you add this configuration element, the system is open to
          the Internet&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;If you added this configuration element, the system would be open to
          the Internet&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exception:&lt;/strong&gt; Use future tense if it&amp;rsquo;s necessary to convey the correct
meaning. This requirement is rare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;address-the-audience-directly&#34;&gt;Address the audience directly&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; in a sentence can be confusing, because the reader may not know
whether they&amp;rsquo;re part of the &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; you&amp;rsquo;re describing. For example, compare the
following two statements:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;In this release we&amp;rsquo;ve added many new features.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;In this tutorial we build a flying saucer.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The words &amp;ldquo;the developer&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;the user&amp;rdquo; can be ambiguous. For example, if the
reader is building a product that also has users, then the reader does not
know whether you&amp;rsquo;re referring to the reader or the users of their product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&#34;table table-bordered&#34;&gt;
    &lt;thead class=&#34;thead-light&#34;&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Address the reader directly&lt;/th&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Instead of &#34;we&#34;, &#34;the user&#34;, or &#34;the developer&#34;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/thead&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;Include the directory in your path&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;The user must make sure that the directory is included in their path
        &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;In this tutorial you build a flying saucer&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;In this tutorial we build a flying saucer&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-short-simple-sentences&#34;&gt;Use short, simple sentences&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep sentences short. Short sentences are easier to read than long ones.
Below are some tips for writing short sentences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&#34;table table-bordered&#34;&gt;
    &lt;thead class=&#34;thead-light&#34;&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;th colspan=&#34;2&#34;&gt;Use fewer words instead of many words that convey the same meaning&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Use this&lt;/th&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Instead of this&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/thead&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;You can use&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;It is also possible to use&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;You can&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;You are able to&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&#34;table table-bordered&#34;&gt;
    &lt;thead class=&#34;thead-light&#34;&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;th colspan=&#34;2&#34;&gt;Split a single long sentence into two or more shorter ones&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Use this&lt;/th&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Instead of this&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/thead&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;You do not need a running GKE cluster. The deployment process
          creates a cluster for you&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;You do not need a running GKE cluster, because the deployment 
          process creates a cluster for you&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&#34;table table-bordered&#34;&gt;
    &lt;thead class=&#34;thead-light&#34;&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;th colspan=&#34;2&#34;&gt;Use a list instead of a long sentence showing various options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Use this&lt;/th&gt;
        &lt;th&gt;Instead of this&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/thead&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;To train a model:&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;ol&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Package your program in a Kubernetes container.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Upload the container to an online registry.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Submit your training job.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;/ol&gt;
        &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;To train a model, you must package your program in a Kubernetes 
          container, upload the container to an online registry, and submit your 
          training job.&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;avoid-too-much-text-styling&#34;&gt;Avoid too much text styling&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use &lt;strong&gt;bold text&lt;/strong&gt; when referring to UI controls or other UI elements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use &lt;code&gt;code style&lt;/code&gt; for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;filenames, directories, and paths&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;inline code and commands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;object field names&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Avoid using bold text or capital letters for emphasis. If a page has too much
textual highlighting it becomes confusing and even annoying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-angle-brackets-for-placeholders&#34;&gt;Use angle brackets for placeholders&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;export KUBEFLOW_USERNAME=&amp;lt;your username&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;--email &amp;lt;your email address&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;style-your-images&#34;&gt;Style your images&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kubeflow docs recognise Bootstrap classes to style images and other content.
The following code snippet shows the typical styling that makes an
image show up nicely on the page:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/docs/images/my-image.png&amp;quot;
  alt=&amp;quot;My image&amp;quot;
  class=&amp;quot;mt-3 mb-3 p-3 border border-info rounded&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;To see some examples of styled images, take a look at the
&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/gke/deploy/oauth-setup/&#34;&gt;OAuth setup page&lt;/a&gt;.
To see the markup, search for &lt;code&gt;.png&lt;/code&gt; in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kubeflow/website/master/content/en/docs/gke/deploy/oauth-setup.md&#34;&gt;page
source&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more help, see the guide to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://getbootstrap.com/docs/4.0/content/images/&#34;&gt;Bootstrap image styling&lt;/a&gt;
and the Bootstrap utilities, such as
&lt;a href=&#34;https://getbootstrap.com/docs/4.0/utilities/borders/&#34;&gt;borders&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-detailed-style-guide&#34;&gt;A detailed style guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.google.com/style/&#34;&gt;Google Developer Documentation Style
Guide&lt;/a&gt;
contains detailed information about specific aspects of writing clear, readable,
succinct documentation for a developer audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;next-steps&#34;&gt;Next steps&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/website/blob/master/README.md&#34;&gt;documentation
README&lt;/a&gt; for
guidance on contributing to the Kubeflow docs.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide: Events Calendar</title>
      <link>/guide/about/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guide/about/events/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This is a nonexhaustive list of events (in reverse chronological order) with talks and workshops about Kubeflow.
Please edit this page and send a pull request, or raise a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/website/issues/new&#34;&gt;GitHub issue&lt;/a&gt;, if something is missing or incorrect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/website/wiki/Kubeflow-Doc-Sprint&#34;&gt;Kubeflow Doc Sprint - Sunnyvale and online&lt;/a&gt;,
10-12 February 2020
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monday 10 February:&lt;/em&gt; Welcome; docs/code development; learning sessions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tuesday 11 February:&lt;/em&gt; Sprint updates; docs/code development; learning sessions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wednesday 12 February:&lt;/em&gt; Docs/code development; sprint demos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kubeflow Doc Sprint, 10-12 July 2019. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/kubeflow/kubeflow-doc-sprint-its-a-wrap-2683bfd4078d&#34;&gt;results of the July 2019 doc sprint&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud.withgoogle.com/next/sf&#34;&gt;Google Cloud Next, San Francisco&lt;/a&gt;, 9-11 April, 2019
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud.withgoogle.com/next/sf/sessions?session=MLAI206&#34;&gt;Undoing Human Bias at Scale With Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt;: John Bohannon, Michelle Casbon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/14Jr79aWVjsJg8xq38CLVE4rKRwM1_-gHLuxhGAhrGTI/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Kubeflow Contributor Summit 2019&lt;/a&gt;, Sunnyvale, CA, 12-13 March, 2019
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kubeflow and the ML Landscape: Jeremy Lewi, Google
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1kJtBNOLHI8bR7z5OVUNDQHUBJ0K7ayGPwP4UQezMAoA/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updates from the PM Working Group:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PMs: David Aronchick, Josh Bottum, Carmine Rimi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/100GXMDDKDyiANSZnvIN_l5kCNxKnsOOcTLq-34-OaJc/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building Together: Community in Kubeflow: Thea Lamkin, Google
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1kEOkz82lUJEfr0GrfDLnTN-g7D1NaFyvqBAzuEDjce8/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiment Tracking with Kubeflow, Lukas Biewald, Weights &amp;amp; Biases
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/a/kubeflow.org/file/d/1JEqNlDHk9LKe8QZ0lUQc7X09Y_59Zyga/view?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multi-User Environments, Kam Kasravi &amp;amp; Ebi Shahbazi, Intel
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1xoqu189q54sAXRTQ-Ise3_T09JLkQxVBGe5lCFy4UsE/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On-Premise: Debo Dutta, Cisco
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1cphcFf4qszQ9PxcEnYkF0pkY3AZEQiEEjs8cso2KJjE/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MiniKF: Local Kubeflow: Vangelis Koukis, Arrikto
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1ftOhRZtpIF3Iy-2R6z9kwgS3KMUtIFnvA1LHHEyxsp8/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TensorFlow 2.0 is coming!: Paige Bailey, Google
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1G0BE7tvhsCzZn2uaxEZsoosEZyXkjN8CnB3uHvLpiC0/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overview of Kubeflow Pipelines: Pavel Dournov, Google
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1aMmJUz7r7Toky4nGZ1bItWKfXW4kSMbs4cofFeyKE-M/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feast: Feature Storage for Machine Learning: Tim Sell, Google
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1k2FrlIyob3UfzvzxJ7B8YI9H3dx8B-LTDqCH_FESYCA/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding the Earth: Machine Learning with Kubeflow Pipelines: Faustine Li, Descartes Labs
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/17KeqJmoKM0hBnXDiC5X2qEPutX08TmL56RyTWMbQ34w/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kubeflow Experiments at LinkedIn: Tengfei Mu &amp;amp; Abin Shahab, LinkedIn
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1bnVZXCvNKOtmqCIMefT2QZCQb62_P0pwBa3PBachNus/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ask the User: Data Science Panel, Moderator: Karthik Ramasamy, Google
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Panelists: Ting Chen, Emmanuel Ameisen, Scott Leishman, Caio Soares, June Andrews, Jun Wang&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simple, GPU-Accelerated Kubeflow Pipeline: Ananth Sankarasubramanian, NVIDIA
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1B84ix3Dq_s-vj0wRagKGEUtyT4Euhr_siY8oCG-zW1w/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fairing: Matt Rickard, Google
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1-gqS-HxMpMd2Kv5-W1_i2TQuXO8O_oM1mL0s-7I2-bA/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ModelDB: Open-source model management: Manasi Vartak, Verta.ai
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1ri_GrTNyz1XScbaK5f1isvSeA8pGpURg7lmghv8h4Yw/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Katib &amp;amp; Hyperparameter Tuning: Richard Liu, Google
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1QbF8naUIHHHvOWKq7uA-DP_jmADbgep8nfjOC_zG_JQ/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kubeflow User Experience: Derek Ferguson, JP Morgan Chase
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1l4zZVisA1xG1Ty1TNZrWFnDbY9YZ3tZ1TkLe6UqUSXk/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kubeflow &amp;amp; TFX: Kevin Haas, Google
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1j4q7AkMs2Pz-9VFmE2vKOanqrR7NFIkN22ObJ_7DVm0/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kubeflow inference on Knative: Dan Sun, Bloomberg
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1sApAPkBWEKBVB5KZCJKHAcsy8Ry2TLzTnGLbpN6EiXA/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Arena: Yang Che, Alibaba
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1mZ6pjgUYt0LhGN8E-zCM1FE-3GNbtK8Y6NlVeD1WahY/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/a/kubeflow.org/file/d/1ITkcf9YvYDJ9KiRlNWOHmMEFOe2DeMGi/view?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Demo video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examples, Codelabs, &amp;amp; Demos: Michelle Casbon, Google
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1h001JfBUaAjoPTrHpbuVRNJtrO1jWRMG_YRDzL2Pd3I/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://datadaytexas.com/&#34;&gt;Data Day Texas, Austin&lt;/a&gt;, 26 January, 2019
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://datadaytexas.com/2019/sessions#casbon&#34;&gt;Kubeflow: Portable Machine Learning on Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1PvtKTw3KNbGurNymDddbsmEfLQd9cOfjbpDQ-2DSNd8&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://aisea19.xnextcon.com/&#34;&gt;AI NEXTCon, Seattle&lt;/a&gt;, 23-26 January, 2019
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://aisea19.xnextcon.com/talkabstract.html#ws-kubeflow&#34;&gt;Build and Manage Machine Learning Pipelines&lt;/a&gt;: Amy Unruh&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/events/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2018/&#34;&gt;KubeCon, Seattle&lt;/a&gt;, 11-13 December, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/Ha1X&#34;&gt;Deep Dive: Kubeflow BoF&lt;/a&gt;: Jeremy Lewi, David Aronchick
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1QP-o4O3ygpJ6aVfu6lAm0tMWYhAvdKE9FD6_92DB3EY&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gbZJ8eSIfJg&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/GrTc&#34;&gt;Eco-Friendly ML: How the Kubeflow Ecosystem Bootstrapped Itself&lt;/a&gt;: Peter McKinnon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1DUJHiYxz0D6qexBbNGjtRHYi4ERTKUOZ-LvqoHVKS-E&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EVSfp8HGJXY&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/GrVh&#34;&gt;Machine Learning as Code&lt;/a&gt;: Jay Smith
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1XKyf5fAM9KfF4OSnZREoDu-BP8JBtGkuSv72iX7CARY&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VXrGp5er1ZE&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/GrVn&#34;&gt;Natural Language Code Search for GitHub Using Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt;: Jeremy Lewi, Hamel Husain
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1jHE61fAqZNgaDrpItk5L_tCzLU0DuL86rCz4yAKz4Ss&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SF77UBvfTHU&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/GrWE&#34;&gt;Workshop: Kubeflow End-to-End: GitHub Issue Summarization&lt;/a&gt;: Amy Unruh, Michelle Casbon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://g.co/codelabs/kubecon18&#34;&gt;Codelab&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1FFftSbWidin3opCIl4U0HVPvS6xk17izUFrrMR7e5qk&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UdthJEq8YsA&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.meetup.com/Melbourne-Women-in-Machine-Learning-and-Data-Science/&#34;&gt;Women in ML &amp;amp; Data Science&lt;/a&gt;, Melbourne, 5 December, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.meetup.com/Melbourne-Women-in-Machine-Learning-and-Data-Science/events/256563019/&#34;&gt;Panel&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://melbourne.yowconference.com.au/&#34;&gt;YOW!, Melbourne&lt;/a&gt;, 4-7 December, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://melbourne.yowconference.com.au/proposal/?id=6858&#34;&gt;Kubeflow Explained: NLP Architectures on Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1lXs1B4xrXTK2QiVe5rJSPCQjTdyMDfNVJcZCLh-Bcu0&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://brisbane.yowconference.com.au/&#34;&gt;YOW!, Brisbane&lt;/a&gt;, 3-4 December, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://brisbane.yowconference.com.au/proposal/?id=6859&#34;&gt;Kubeflow Explained: NLP Architectures on Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1lXs1B4xrXTK2QiVe5rJSPCQjTdyMDfNVJcZCLh-Bcu0&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sydney.yowconference.com.au/&#34;&gt;YOW!, Sydney&lt;/a&gt;, 27-30 November, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sydney.yowconference.com.au/proposal/?id=6860&#34;&gt;Kubeflow Explained: NLP Architectures on Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1lXs1B4xrXTK2QiVe5rJSPCQjTdyMDfNVJcZCLh-Bcu0&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://scale.bythebay.io/&#34;&gt;Scale By the Bay, San Francisco&lt;/a&gt;, 15-17 November, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/Fndz&#34;&gt;Data Engineering &amp;amp; AI Panel&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sJd9RRmgCH4&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lfasiallc.com/events/kubecon-cloudnativecon-china-2018/&#34;&gt;KubeCon, Shanghai&lt;/a&gt;, 13-15 November, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/FzGn&#34;&gt;A Tale of Using Kubeflow to Make the Electricity Smarter in China&lt;/a&gt;: Julia Han, Xin Zhang
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://schd.ws/hosted_files/kccncchina2018english/34/XinZhang_JuliaHan_En.pdf&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fad1FsfEvNY&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/FuLr&#34;&gt;A Year of Democratizing ML With Kubernetes &amp;amp; Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt;: David Aronchick, Fei Xue
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1ZuZs32CFPYZ9ub8o8whSK8SA2333UjtAVujRnKJTf2M&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oMlddDdJgEg&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/FuJw&#34;&gt;Benchmarking Machine Learning Workloads on Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt;: Xinyuan Huang, Ce Gao
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://schd.ws/hosted_files/kccncchina2018english/22/Kubebench_KubeCon2018China.pdf&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9sLRIBYYUlQ&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/FuJo&#34;&gt;CI/CD Pipelines &amp;amp; Machine Learning&lt;/a&gt;: Jeremy Lewi
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://schd.ws/hosted_files/kccncchina2018english/ee/KubeConChina2018.pdf&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EH850bIQVag&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/FuJx&#34;&gt;Kubeflow From the End User&amp;rsquo;s Perspective&lt;/a&gt;: Xin Zhang
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x0CKhyoV9aI&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/FuJc&#34;&gt;Kubernetes CI/CD Hacks with KicroK8s and Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt;: Land Lu, Zhang Lei Mao
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://schd.ws/hosted_files/kccncchina2018english/0a/Kubecon%20Shanghai%20-%20CICD%20Hacks_Canonical.pdf&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1SSvS2w5OMQ&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/FuJs&#34;&gt;Machine Learning on Kubernetes BoF&lt;/a&gt;: David Aronchick
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0eEAZ7lmLbo&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/FuJt&#34;&gt;Operating Deep Learning Pipelines Anywhere Using Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt;: Jörg Schad, Gilbert Song
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://schd.ws/hosted_files/kccncchina2018english/fe/Kubecon%20KubeFlow%2B%2B%20Summit.pdf&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=63HJgZK27mU&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/devfest-seattle-2018-tickets-50408043816&#34;&gt;DevFest, Seattle&lt;/a&gt;, 3 November, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kubeflow End to End: Amy Unruh&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dataatscale2018.splashthat.com/&#34;&gt;Data@Scale, Boston&lt;/a&gt;, 25 October, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://datascalewomensbreakfast.splashthat.com/&#34;&gt;Women in Engineering Panel&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://code.fb.com/core-data/data-scale-boston/&#34;&gt;Kubeflow: Portable Machine Learning on Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/atscaleevents/videos/114311602829170/&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kafka-summit.org/&#34;&gt;Kafka Summit, San Francisco&lt;/a&gt;, 16-17 October, 2018&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.oreilly.com/artificial-intelligence/ai-eu&#34;&gt;O’Reilly AI Conference, London&lt;/a&gt;, 08-11 October, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.oreilly.com/artificial-intelligence/ai-eu/public/schedule/detail/69194&#34;&gt;Machine Learning at Scale with Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Chris Cho&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cloud-Native, Docker, and Kubernetes Summit, Dallas, 12 September, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/kubernetes-classes-at-cloud-native-docker-k8s-summit-tickets-44954443952&#34;&gt;Deploying Machine Learning Workloads in Kubernetes clusters that support GPUs&lt;/a&gt;: Michael Iatrou&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.oreilly.com/strata/strata-ny&#34;&gt;O’Reilly Strata Data, New York&lt;/a&gt;, 11-13 September, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.oreilly.com/strata/strata-ny/public/schedule/detail/69362&#34;&gt;From Training to Serving: Deploying TensorFlow Models with Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Brian Foo, Holden Karau, Jay Smith&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.oreilly.com/strata/strata-ny/public/schedule/detail/69041&#34;&gt;Kubeflow Explained: Portable Machine Learning on Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.oreilly.com/artificial-intelligence/ai-ca&#34;&gt;O&amp;rsquo;Reilly AI Conference, San Francisco&lt;/a&gt;, 4-7 September, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.oreilly.com/artificial-intelligence/ai-ca/public/schedule/topic/2899&#34;&gt;TensorFlow Days: Kubeflow: Portable Machine Learning on Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/events/open-source-summit-north-america-2018/&#34;&gt;Open Source Summit, Vancouver&lt;/a&gt;, 29-31 August, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/events/open-source-summit-north-america-2018/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;Elastic AI Pipeline with Kubeflow for Intelligent SKU Management in a Large Chinese Retailer&lt;/a&gt;: Xin Zhang&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/events/open-source-summit-north-america-2018/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;Introducing Kubeflow: A System for Deploying ML/AI on
Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Trevor Grant, Holden Karau&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.oreilly.com/jupyter/jup-ny&#34;&gt;JupyterCon, New York&lt;/a&gt;, 21-25 August, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.oreilly.com/jupyter/jup-ny/public/schedule/detail/69752&#34;&gt;Machine Learning at Scale with Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Chris Cho&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud.withgoogle.com/next18/sf/&#34;&gt;Google Next, San Francisco&lt;/a&gt;, 24-26 July, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AI Platform Showcase demo: Dan Sanche
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=el7cw-nVcBE&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud.withgoogle.com/next18/sf/sessions/session/193227&#34;&gt;Machine Learning Made Easy: How to Build Flexible, Portable ML Stacks with Kubeflow and Elastifile&lt;/a&gt;: David Aronchick, Allon Cohen
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NAqD6siHcpE&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud.withgoogle.com/next18/sf/sessions/session/229041&#34;&gt;Spotlight Lab: Introduction to Kubeflow on Google Kubernetes Engine&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://codelabs.developers.google.com/codelabs/kubeflow-introduction/index.html&#34;&gt;Codelab&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud.withgoogle.com/next18/sf/sessions/session/229637&#34;&gt;Spotlight Lab: Kubeflow End-to-End: GitHub Issue Summarization&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://codelabs.developers.google.com/codelabs/cloud-kubeflow-e2e-gis/index.html&#34;&gt;Codelab&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.oreilly.com/oscon/oscon-or-2018&#34;&gt;O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Open Source Convention, Portland&lt;/a&gt;, 16-19 July, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.oreilly.com/oscon/oscon-or/public/schedule/detail/70899&#34;&gt;TensorFlow Day: Hassle-free, scalable machine learning with Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt;: Barbara Fusinska&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://scipy2018.scipy.org/ehome/index26ac.html?eventid=299527&amp;amp;tabid=712461&amp;amp;cid=2233540&amp;amp;sessionid=21618893&amp;amp;sessionchoice=1&amp;amp;%26&#34;&gt;SciPy, Austin&lt;/a&gt;, 09-15 July, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kubeflow: Pythonic Machine Learning at Scale on Kubernetes: David Aronchick, Paige Bailey
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b_CvqzmB51M&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://paris-container-day.fr/en/&#34;&gt;Container Day, Paris&lt;/a&gt;, 26 June, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://paris-container-day.fr/en/#tabidff38a849e758226764f1da33f5bd81e3&#34;&gt;Keynote: Cloud Native ML with Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt;: David Aronchick, Chris Cho
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rcC11EZdo8Y&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2018.dockercon.com/&#34;&gt;Dockercon, San Francisco&lt;/a&gt;, 12 - 15 June, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dockercon18.smarteventscloud.com/connect/sessionDetail.ww?SESSION_ID=224348&#34;&gt;Keynote: Moby&amp;rsquo;s Cool Hacks&lt;/a&gt;: David Aronchick, Michelle Casbon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/RnWXOAplvjY?t=1128&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://qconsp.com/sp2018/schedule/tabular.html&#34;&gt;QCon, São Paulo&lt;/a&gt;, 9-11 May, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://qconsp.com/sp2018/sp2018/presentation/architecture-nlp-deployment.html&#34;&gt;Architecture of an NLP Deployment&lt;/a&gt;: Michelle Casbon
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SbecYkirt8w&amp;amp;t=1975&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/events/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2018/&#34;&gt;KubeCon, Copenhagen&lt;/a&gt;, 2-4 May, 2018
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interview: Building applications on Kubeflow: Jeremy Lewi
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VTGH9ocdVM0&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccnceu18.sched.com/event/Duoq/keynote-cloud-native-ml-on-kubernetes-david-aronchick-product-manager-cloud-ai-and-co-founder-of-kubeflow-google-vishnu-kannan-sr-software-engineer-google-slides-attached&#34;&gt;Keynote: Cloud Native ML on Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: David Aronchick, Vishnu Kannan
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I6iMznIYwM8&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1_QxDZXX-sSP8llFZQ6T2zseZOcPFuVLk/view?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccnceu18.sched.com/event/Drnd/kubeflow-deep-dive-david-aronchick-jeremy-lewi-google-intermediate-skill-level&#34;&gt;Kubeflow Deep Dive&lt;/a&gt;: David Aronchick, Jeremy Lewi
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=86GD1VzSnks&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/url?q=https%3A%2F%2Fschd.ws%2Fhosted_files%2Fkccnceu18%2Fd4%2FKubeflow_Deep_Dive.pdf&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFK_-mkyWfKAFM9wnywPVYH9thoYw&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccnceu18.sched.com/event/Drmt/kubeflow-intro-michal-jastrzebski-ala-raddaoui-intel-any-skill-level-slides-attached&#34;&gt;Kubeflow Intro&lt;/a&gt;: Michał Jastrzębski, Ala Raddaoui
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NrDpQks0e98&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://schd.ws/hosted_files/kccnceu18/9f/kubeflow-intro.pdf&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccnceu18.sched.com/event/Dqvw/serving-ml-models-at-scale-with-seldon-and-kubeflow-clive-cox-seldonio-intermediate-skill-level-slides-attached&#34;&gt;Serving ML Models at Scale with Seldon &amp;amp; Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt;: Clive Cox
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pDlapGtecbY&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://schd.ws/hosted_files/kccnceu18/1a/SeldonKubeconEurope2018.pdf&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccnceu18.sched.com/event/Dqv6/conquering-a-kubeflow-kubernetes-cluster-with-ksonnet-ark-and-sonobuoy-kris-nova-heptio-david-aronchick-google-intermediate-skill-level&#34;&gt;Conquering a Kubeflow Kubernetes Cluster with ksonnet, Ark, &amp;amp; Sonobuoy&lt;/a&gt;: David Aronchick, Kris Nova
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=givpqZ2IchI&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccnceu18.sched.com/event/Dquu/building-ml-products-with-kubeflow-jeremy-lewi-google-stephan-fabel-canonical-intermediate-skill-level-slides-attached&#34;&gt;Building ML Products with Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt;: Jeremy Lewi, Stephan Fabel
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sC8Ce9vUggo&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://schd.ws/hosted_files/kccnceu18/c2/Building%20ML%20Products%20With%20Kubeflow%20%28Kubecon%202018%29%20%281%29.pdf&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccnceu18.sched.com/event/DqvC/compliant-data-management-and-machine-learning-on-kubernetes-daniel-whitenack-pachyderm-intermediate-skill-level-slides-attached&#34;&gt;Compliant Data Management &amp;amp; Machine Learning on Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;: Daniel Whitenack
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eOzl-LFqYFM&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://schd.ws/hosted_files/kccnceu18/a1/KubeCon_EU_2018%20%281%29.pdf&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccnceu18.sched.com/event/E46y/bringing-your-data-pipeline-into-the-machine-learning-era-chris-gaun-jorg-schad-mesosphere-intermediate-skill-level&#34;&gt;Bringing Your Data Pipeline into the Machine Learning Era&lt;/a&gt;: Chris Gaun, Jörg Schad
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f_-3rQoudnc&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://events17.linuxfoundation.org/events/kubecon-and-cloudnativecon-north-america&#34;&gt;KubeCon, Austin&lt;/a&gt;, 6-8 December, 2017
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna17.sched.com/event/CU5v/hot-dogs-or-not-at-scale-with-kubernetes-i-vish-kannan-david-aronchick-google&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hot Dog or Not Hot Dog&amp;rdquo; at Scale - Kubernetes &amp;amp; Machine Learning&lt;/a&gt;: David Aronchick, Vishnu Kannan
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R3dVF5wWz-g&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
